{
    "subject": "Alan_Rudolph",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Love_at_Large",
    "human_readable": "Alan Rudolph directed the film Love at Large.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9022719264030457,
            "question": "Who directed the film Love at Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8135923147201538,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6872351765632629,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Love at Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6589587330818176,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in the film Love at Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6414368748664856,
            "question": "Where was the film Love at Large filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6324220299720764,
            "question": "What year was the film Love at Large released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6148010492324829,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5246000289916992,
            "question": "What themes are explored in the film Love at Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5048499703407288,
            "question": "What genre is the film Love at Large likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24373658001422882,
            "question": "Has Alan Rudolph won any awards for his films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Rudolph directed the film Love at Large.",
            "html": "yago_9763_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Love at Large likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_9763_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes are explored in the film Love at Large?",
            "html": "yago_9763_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films directed by Alan Rudolph?",
            "html": "yago_9763_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9763_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Alan Rudolph wrote and directed the film \"Love at Large\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that Alan Rudolph directed the film \"Love at Large,\" such as in file_path 7 and 15."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}